picsity.com 2013-11-26

# Terms / Privacy on Picsity

### The following privacy policy will help you understand the information we collect, how we use it, and what choices you have regarding your information.

Picsity operates this website ("Site") and is committed to protecting the privacy of its visitors. Your use of this Site indicates your acceptance of this Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy"). If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, you may not use the Site.

### Collecting Information

By providing us with your personal information, you consent to the collection, storage, processing, use and disclosure of your personal data as provided in this Policy. We may collect certain information from you when you set up your account with us, when you update your account, and when you use certain other features on our site, such as making purchases. We collect payment information, such as credit card number, as well as contact information, including, but not limited to address, email address and phone number. We may also collect demographic information about you and information about your shopping or other personal preferences. 

We may also gather certain information concerning the use of the Site, such as page visits, through the use of cookies or other technologies. Cookies are used to transfer information to us through your web browser and are used for recordkeeping and/or analytical purposes. They are also used to customize content for you on the Site or for storage of information between pages or visits. 

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies. However, you may adjust your browser settings to reject cookies or to notify you when one is being used. Many of the features on our Site depends on the use of cookies and will not function properly without them. Therefore, it is necessary for your web browser to accept cookies for you to access the Site. 

### Use of Your Information

We will not share or disclose your personal information to anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

We use personally identifiable information in order to give you a more enjoyable convenient shopping experience and to help us identify and/or provide information, products, or services that may be of interest to you. We use your personally identifiable information to support and enhance your use of the Site and its features, including, but no limited to: fulfilling your order; providing customer service; tracking email invitations you send; etc. We may also track your past purchases or bidding history to provide you with a personalized profile of your shopping history. 

In order to maintain a high level of service and for the operation of the Site, we may allow access of your information to certain trusted third parties. For example, we may use a third party to host the site; operate various features available on the site; etc. 

We may transfer personally identifiable information in connection with a proposed or actual merger or sale involving all or part of our business or as part of a corporate reorganization. In such circumstances, the Transferee would be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

We may disclose information in order to comply with a subpoena, court order, administrative or government order, or any other requirement of law, or when we, in our sole discretion, believe it is necessary in order to protect our rights or the rights of others, to prevent harm to persons or property, to fight fraud and credit risk reduction. 

### External Links

The Site may contain links to external websites. These websites follow their own policies regarding the collection and use of personal information. It is at your own discretion to review these policies for yourself. Picsity is not responsible for the privacy practices of these external websites. 

### Protecting Your Information

We are committed to protect your information. We follow reasonable technical and management practices to protect the confidentiality, security, and integrety of data stored. We utilize measures that we believe reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved. 

The Site encrypts your credit card number and other personal information using secure socket layer (SSL) technology to provide secure transmission of the information from your computer to our servers. One way to tell if you are on a secure page is to look at the address or URL of the webpage. Secure SSL-encrypted pages have URLs that begin with "https://" (unsecured pages begin with "http://"). 

Your account and profile, including your personal information, is accessible with your personal log-in and password. It is your responsibility to protect your password in order to prevent unauthorized access to your account and personal information. You are responsible for all activites that occur on your account. You also agree to immediately notify us in the event of any unauthorized use of your account or other breach of security. 

### Updating Your Personal Information and Preferences

If you are a registered user, you may access and update your account profile information by logging into your account through the Site. You may change your preferences, including whether to receive or not to receive email or other communications from us. 

Any user who receives an email invitation to join Picsity may choose not to receive such invitations in the future by following the instructions in the email invitation. We will take commercially reasonable steps to implement all opt-out requests promptly, but you may still receive communications from us for up to ten business days as we process your request. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may, from time to time, change this Privacy Policy. The revised Privacy Policy will be posted here with a new effective date so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use it, and how we may disclose it to anyone. 

Effective Date: Feburary 21, 2013
